[
    {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "1 - 1",
        "answers": [
            0,
            1,
            2,
            3
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 0,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "2 - 1",
        "answers": [
            1,
            2,
            3,
            4
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "3 - 1",
        "answers": [
            2,
            3,
            4,
            5
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 2,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "4 - 1",
        "answers": [
            2,
            3,
            4,
            5
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 3,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "5 - 1",
        "answers": [
            2,
            3,
            4,
            5
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 4,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "2 - 2",
        "answers": [
            0,
            1,
            2,
            3
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 0,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "3 - 2",
        "answers": [
            0,
            1,
            2,
            3
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "4 - 2",
        "answers": [
            0,
            1,
            2,
            3
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 2,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "5 - 2",
        "answers": [
            0,
            1,
            2,
            3
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 3,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "3 - 3",
        "answers": [
            0,
            1,
            2,
            3
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 0,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 11,
        "question": "4 - 3",
        "answers": [
            0,
            1,
            2,
            3
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 12,
        "question": "5 - 3",
        "answers": [
            0,
            1,
            2,
            3
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 2,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 13,
        "question": "4 - 4",
        "answers": [
            0,
            1,
            2,
            3
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 0,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 14,
        "question": "5 - 4",
        "answers": [
            0,
            1,
            2,
            3
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 15,
        "question": "5 - 5",
        "answers": [
            0,
            1,
            2,
            3
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 0,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 16,
        "question": "9 - 5",
        "answers": [
            3,
            4,
            5,
            6
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 4,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 17,
        "question": "8 - 4",
        "answers": [
            2,
            3,
            4,
            5
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 4,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 18,
        "question": "7 - 2",
        "answers": [
            5,
            6,
            7,
            8
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 5,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 19,
        "question": "7 - 3",
        "answers": [
            2,
            3,
            4,
            5
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 4,
        "clicked": false
    },
    {
        "id": 20,
        "question": "6 - 5",
        "answers": [
            0,
            1,
            2,
            3
        ],
        "correctAnswer": 1,
        "clicked": false
    }
]